{
    "config": {
        "color": "#644e9b"
    },
    "Title": {
        "question": "My Label Maker isn't working",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "My screen isn't working",
                "nextStep": "Screen"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A tape motor isn't working",
                "nextStep": "Motor"
            },
            {
                "answer": "My servo isn't working",
                "nextStep": "Servo"
            },
            {
                "answer": "My joystick isn't working",
                "nextStep": "Joystick"
            },
            {
                "answer": "It won't turn on",
                "nextStep": "Power"
            }
        ]
    },
    "Screen": {
        "question": "Push the arduino firmly into the breadboard, it might click into place. Does it work now?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "CheckBacklight"
            }
        ]
    },
    "CheckBacklight": {
        "question": "Is the backlight on?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "ReplaceLCD"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Yes",
                "nextStep": "LCDAnotherArduino"
            }
        ]
    },
    "ReplaceLCD": {
        "question": "Contact CrunchLabs for a replacement screen",
        "answers": []
    },
    "LCDAnotherArduino": {
        "question": "Try uploading Label Maker code to a different Arduino from ide.crunchlabs.com, and use this arduino. Does it work now?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "ReplaceLCD"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Yes",
                "nextStep": "ReplacementArduino"
            }
        ]
    },
    "ReplacementArduino": {
        "question": "Contact CrunchLabs for a replacement Arduino",
        "answers": []
    },
    "Motor": {
        "question": "Is the motor going backwards?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes",
                "nextStep": "BackwardsFix"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "MotorAnotherArduino"
            }
        ]
    },
    "BackwardsFix": {
        "question": "Take the 4 signal wires for the backwards motor, and flip them around in the breadboard",
        "answers": []
    },
    "MotorAnotherArduino": {
        "question": "Try uploading Label Maker code to a different Arduino from ide.crunchlabs.com, and use this arduino. Does it work now?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "SwapMotorsCheck"
            }
        ]
    },
    "SwapMotorsCheck": {
        "question": "If a motor isn't working, swap which motor is plugged into which driver, you will need to unscrew a driver from the wall to reach. Does the broken axis swap to being the other motor?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes",
                "nextStep": "ReplacementDriver"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "ReplacementMotor"
            }
        ]
    },
    "ReplacementDriver": {
        "question": "Contact CrunchLabs for a replacement driver",
        "answers": []
    },
    "ReplacementMotor": {
        "question": "Contact CrunchLabs for a replacement Stepper Motor",
        "answers": []
    },
    "Servo": {
        "question": "Is the servo moving or making sound?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes",
                "nextStep": "ReplacementServo"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "ServoHelp"
            }
        ]
    },
    "ReplacementServo": {
        "question": "Contact CrunchLabs for a replacement servo",
        "answers": []
    },
    "ServoHelp": {
        "question": "Contact CrunchLabs for additional help",
        "answers": []
    },
    "Joystick": {
        "question": "Push the arduino firmly into the breadboard, it might click into place. Does it work now?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "ReplacementJoystick"
            }
        ]
    },
    "ReplacementJoystick": {
        "question": "Contact CrunchLabs for a replacement joystick",
        "answers": []
    },
    "Power": {
        "question": "Push the arduino firmly into the breadboard, it might click into place. Did it turn on?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "CheckBackwardsWires"
            }
        ]
    },
    "CheckBackwardsWires": {
        "question": "Make sure you don't have red and black wires backwards. Does it turn on now?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "No",
                "nextStep": "TryAnotherBattery"
            }
        ]
    },
    "TryAnotherBattery": {
        "question": "Try a charged battery from another Hack Pack. Does it turn on now?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes",
                "nextStep": "ReplacementBattery"
            }
        ]
    },
    "ReplacementBattery": {
        "question": "Charge your battery, if it still doesn't work contact CrunchLabs for a replacement battery",
        "answers": []
    }
}